That's London actually.
Yeah, it's yeah, with this weather signal starts
arriving actually.
Yeah.
Yeah, all good. Thank
you.
Yeah. Hi, I'm Daniel Bird.
I'm the customer support manager here at Praktika
and Praktika. We are an education app specifically
for language learning.
So we use AI avatars or AI toolers so that users
can have normal conversations and practice pronunciation.
And thanks to our app, I mean users have been
doing amazingly in terms of uh learning a new
language. Either that's Mandarin, uh Russian,
Arabic, English, or any language that you that
you think about. And um yeah, thank you very
much for for being
here.
Well well, yeah, I mean that's a that's a great
question. So I love Mach 1.
I think uh it's a great platform, very intuitively,
and it's become one of our let's say biggest
partners for helping us I mean manage every
kind of request that we get from our users.
So we're using Mach 1 and we develop an AI
agent with Mach 1 specifically for the customer
support or customer success team.
And this agent we call it Myra.
Uh I mean has, doing a great job in in helping
us resolve all the different queries and questions
from users. Um, and yeah, I love the platform
because it's very easy to use.
I mean, I have an engineering background, not
necessarily a software engineer or machine learning
engineer background, but it's been very easy
for me to every day iteratively use the platform
so that we can improve uh our workflows and
also the way Myra responds to our users.
Uh and yeah, I pretty much use Mach 1 every
day.
So we use, I mean, we call it different logics,
let's say, uh, because our workflows are quite
complex. So a user might be requesting from
some information from the app, some functionalities
that they don't understand.
But also, we have some let's say actions taken
by this uh agent that could be, for example,
renewing a subscription or potentially canceling
a subscription, refunding a subscription.
So uh it's quite complex our workflow because
depending on the request of the user, uh, our
agent will be doing a set of different tasks
requested by users every time, of course, following
our context and our policies.
So I've been in a company for a couple of months
already, and actually my role has been changed
a lot thanks to the introduction of Mach 1,
or let's say Myra to our company.
So when I start when I joined Praktika, I was
essentially an agent responding to all of these
tickets, mainly because I wanted to learn specifically
about how to answer to all of these queries,
uh, the language, the tone, right?
How to answer to all these queries.
And now slowly my role has been transitioning
a bit into now managing Myra.
Uh and I'm managing Myra on a daily basis, uh,
so that uh Myra can be improving their questions.
I think I'm sorry, I think I'm cutting a bit.
Uh if not, I'll I'll repeat the answer.
Uh can you hear
me?
Yeah.